

# Nguyen Dang Khuong

<>Front-end developer</>



Oct 22, 1996



0336605149



nguyendangkhuong96@gmail.com



**9** 394, Ung Van Khiem

## **Skills**

- React (Redux-thunk/saga/ toolkit), Next.js, Typescript
- NodeJS(Express), MongoDB
- Wordpress (SCSS, PlainJS)
- · Restfull api, axios, graphql, grpcclient, apollo, react-query
- · Adobe illustrator, figma, Xd
- Material-ui, Ant-design, Semantic-UI, Tailwind-ui, charka-
- CI-CD with docker and circle-ci
- · Git, github, gitlab
- Jira, Asana Agile, Scrum

# **Links and Credentials**



in Linkedin



<u>Github</u>



<u>Website</u>

# **Hobbies & Interest**

- Coding
- Gaming
- Movie
- Crypto, block chain

#### **About**

I'm a front end developer with an emphasis on clean responsive design. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. JavaScript expert and React JS, delighted about the constantly evolving world of front-end web who finds ways to express complicated ideas through intuitive design.

# **Experience**



#### LIG TECHNOLOGIES VIETNAM

React developer - Wordpress developer | 7/2021 - present

- · Work for asoview with all asoview's project (because asoview and lig are partners, lig acquires asoview)
- Work with wordpress to build homepage web: liginc.vn and lamp project: https://lamp-guesthouse.com/



### **ASOVIEW VIET NAM**

React developer | 6/2018 - 6/2021

- Develop high performance customer facing e-commerce application using Reacjs, Nextjs, Redux-thunk, React Hooks, React-Router, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, Ant design.
- Developed custom API layer and custom hook to handle all CRUD transactions, JWT token management and implemented interceptors to embed custom headers.
- · Maintained high-level expertise in React state management strategies, including ImmutableJS, Redux, Redux-thunk, duck pattern.
- · Worked closely with clients to establish specifications and system designs. Used Figma, Xd to collaborate with UX.
- Expertise usage of Git and JIRA as a version control and tracking units.
- · Support and help members solve problems. Sometime support back-end with java language.
- · Projects: asoview.com, internal-manager, asoview-gift, satsuki, asoview-ticket, asoview-global, asoview.vn, agent

#### **©**vtech

# Vtech web (intern)

Front-end developer - PHP developer | 11/2017 - 5/2018

- · Support to create the sales page of the company https://vtechweb.com/
- Practice website sales by laravel framework (PHP)

#### **Education**

7/2015 - 7/2018

 VNUHCM-University Of Science Major: Information Technology (Web developer)